Contact





kirankumarbehera87@g mail.com

hiran-kumar-behera-78b553191

Skills

Account reconciliation specialist

Tax Reconcillation

SAP

CIMS

MS Office Suite

Bookkeeping

Internal Audit

Software

SAP

LOTUS

MS OFFICE

TALLY ERP 9

CIMS



Kiran Kumar **Behera**

Accountant

Knowledgeable accounting professional bringing 3.2 years of experience in construction industry. Successful at revamping and strengthening controls, reorganizing processes and simplifying procedures to maximize efficiency and accuracy of accounting records. Experience in CIMS and SAP. Excellent reputation for resolving problems, Audit report, and driving overall operational improvements.

Work History

2020-12 -Current

Junior Account Assistant

Randstad India Pvt Ltd, Bhubaneswar

Client-Orissa Bridge and Construction Corporation Ltd-Government of Orissa, Works Department

- Strengthened financial management processes to bring errors to near-zero in reporting and general bookkeeping.
- Completed daily cash functions like account tracking, payroll and wage allocations,
- Managed entire accounting cycle including gathering information, preparing documents, finalizing reports and closing books.

2019-12 – 2020-12

Accountant

Hajee A.P Bava Construction Pvt Ltd, Udaipur, Rajasthan

- Strengthened financial management processes to bring errors to near-zero in reporting and general bookkeeping.
- Helped clients navigate interactions with tax authorities and legal concerns related to financial matters.
- Completed daily cash functions like account tracking, payroll and wage allocations, budgeting, donating and all types of cash and

Languages

Hindi English Odia

- banking reconciliations.
- Managed entire accounting cycle including gathering information, preparing documents, finalizing reports and closing books.
- Proactively researched technical tax issues related to consulting projects.

2018-12 - Internal Auditor

2019-11 AMULYA ASSOCIATE IN ASSOCIATED WITH TATA STEEL LTD, JAJPUR ROAD, ODISHA

- Performed strategic planning, execution and finalization of audits.
- Investigated discrepancies discovered during auditing process.
- Prepared suitable reports on risk and information gleaned from audits and distributed to appropriate personnel.
- walkthroughs for compliance with documented processes.
- Implemented all auditing information into spreadsheets utilizing.
- Identified and reported audit issues.
- Ensured compliance with JUSCO LTD and TATA STEEL LTD regulations.
- Recommended new methods to improve internal controls and operating efficiency.
- Produced audit reports.

Education

Intermediate: Intermediate in Commerce
 Ravenshaw Junior College - Cuttack

 Bachelor of Commerce: Accountancy
 Utkal University - Bhubaneswar

Graduated with 6.96 CGPA

Kiran Kumar Behera Signature